blindhypnosis.com 2019-10-12

# Privacy Policy (IMPORTANT) - Blind Hypnosis

We commit to protect the personal information of our customers. Information collected by us will be solely used to provide better user interface and support, your Information shared with us will never be distributed, sold or rented to third party bodies

The privacy policy relates to all services, free and paid products and browsed elements offered by blindhypnosis.com

## Information we collect

We will not collect a single personal detail or information without your consent. Information will be collected and stored using latest firewalls and by following network control protocols to ensure maximum confidentiality. 

  * **Personal User Identity** : customer personal information such as e-mail address, name, user-defined password, email confirmation and date of birth (or age) will be collected when user will register on our web page or while placing an order. We will never ask for your critical information such as bank details account passwords or credit card information.
  * **Non-personal information** : apart from customer personal information (required for registration) we will collect information such as the type of device (mobile or desktop), type of browser you use, similar environment information primarily for compatibility and other technical issues.

## Why do we require your personal information? 

We require your personal details while registration, placing orders, customer request offers, similar products and response to surveys on our website. Some other techs for which we require your details are as follows. 

  1. To improve user experience on our website and to provide best results based on customer search.
  2. To maximise the speed, reducing the load time and a number of https requests send to servers.
  3. To improve our services in future for customer related issues and query.
  4. To process web downloads and transitions in a quick and easy way.
  5. To improve advertisement, services, and other services.

## Redirect Chains or links

We will never redirect our users to any third party websites, links & chains, services, or offers. However, if you are redirected in response to network failures or any other unknown issue we will not be responsible for the loss or damage caused by those websites. 

## Unsubscribe

For any reason, if you no longer want to get updates from us users are free to unsubscribe from our service updates anytime. Unsubscribe button is embedded with every email we have sent. 

## Change or Update to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to our policy at any time as per the direction of Government and board members. Changes will be highlighted on the notice board (homepage) of our website and subscribed costumes will receive an auto updated e-mail in their message box listing all the variations. 

## Advice or Questions regarding our Privacy policy

We welcome our users for any advice or complaints regarding the privacy policy of our website. Feel free to contact us in our [contact us](https://blindhypnosis.com/contact.html) section.
